Now let's take a look at how to adjust the fingers on the outer layer of multi-layered clothing.
In many cases, we just cut out one layer of the clothing.
We can remove the joint and enlarge the outer layer of the multi-layered clothing in the same way as before.
Freeze the bottom layer to prevent deformation.
After opening the simulation, we will find that the effect is different from what we expected.
The spine does not only exist in the book.
It can even be said to be pulled into a line.
This is because the sewing line generated by the cologne layer is a whole circle of sewing line, so the length difference is also divided into a whole circle.
In order to concentrate the spine in the vertical direction, we need to sew the line section by section.
After zooming in, you can see that the spine direction is now only in the vertical direction.
In addition to directly changing the pattern,
we can also use the shrink tool to achieve a similar effect.
Using the editing texture tool, we can distinguish the golden tail of the fabric.
The tip of the arrow is the mirror, and the vertical direction is the tail.
For the newly created version of Marvelous Designer, the default value direction is the mirror, and the horizontal direction is the tail.
For example, if you want to form some vertical wrinkles, then the horizontal direction needs to be widened, which is to improve the tail shrink.
This method can also be used to preview the effect of widening or lengthening the entire panel.
Through the grid, we can see that this method is just widening the grid in a certain direction, and it is not like adjusting the panel.
Increasing the number of grid faces, you can choose to keep the shrink effect or directly modify the panel according to your own choice.
Next, let's try to create a spine in a specific position.
Now we have an internal line.
Using the extension tool, we can open the panel along its horizontal direction.
If we sew directly after opening, the spine position is wrong.
This is the same as the previous situation, because a whole long line is sewn to another whole line, so the insertion is divided.
So, using the free sewing tool,
first sew the part that does not change the length.
Then sew the remaining part together.
In this way, the gap is fixed on the left side of the panel.
Drag the panel, and there is a fold.
Then this internal line reference line can be deleted.
To be smoother, we can growth the straight line point into a curved line point.
Like this, this sample is very straightforward.
If we keep using theiyorsun tool, we can reduce the bias.
The angle of the model is in right hand position.
If we keep this signal line to the center, it will berect.
Then, we can adjust the opening 선.
Thank you.